Dragoljub Ranđelović



randjelovicdragoljub1@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/drazzardaq



+38169698442



https://drazzard42.com

Summary

My specialties are web and application development, alongside graphic design.

I can cover a wide range of technologies but prefer Laravel, Vue.js, and Tailwind CSS. AWS, hosting, domains, and DevOps are also the scopes of my specialties.

I've been working in the IT industry for the past 13+ years. I consider myself a creative, intuitive, and eclectic person.

Looking forward to connecting with you.

Experience



CTO and Founder

Adaxions

May 2017 - Present (6 years 1 month)

Web Developer

SEYPRO - Elite African Marketing

Dec 2021 - May 2023 (1 year 6 months)

IT Consultant

NTOS

May 2020 - Feb 2021 (10 months)

Joomla Developer

XENOVATION

Mar 2018 - Aug 2018 (6 months)

Junior Java Developer

MicroBusiness

Oct 2015 - Feb 2016 (5 months)

Search Engine Optimization Manager

Creative Net FX

Oct 2013 - May 2014 (8 months)

Frontend Developer

Creative Net FX

Mar 2013 - Sep 2013 (7 months)

Transport Foreign Exchange Consultant

TeleTrade Europe Jul 2012 - Mar 2013 (9 months)

Transport Client Portfolio Manager

TeleTrade Europe Sep 2011 - May 2012 (9 months)

Education

Megatrend University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Oct 2010 - Present

ICT College of Vocational Studies

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology Oct 2008 - Present

Skills

IT Consulting • English • Front-End Development • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • PHP • Laravel • Vue.js • MySQL • Databases • User Experience Design (UED)